Demid Strukov

Game Developer

Last update: 10.06.2024

Poland

- **3** 27 July 1998
- +48 782 508 702
- https://github.com/CrishNate
- https://gitlab.com/CrishNate
- @crishnate
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/demidstrukov-45887317b
- <u>★ https://crishnate.github.io/portfolio</u>

Personal

A skilled game developer with over 5 years of experience, that is enjoy creating games as much as playing them. Focused on in-game AI systems. Communicative and ready to seek new opportunities in education and self-improvement. Passionate about helping people and mentoring them.

Skills

Programming Languages

- C/C++
- C#
- Python
- Lua

Tools & Technologies

- Unreal 4/5
- Unity
- GAS
- VS / Rider
- VSC (Git,
- PIX
- Perforce)

• Blender 3D

Photoshop

Fields

- Gameplay
- Al / Al Design
- Optimization
- Shader
- ToolsUser Interface
- AnimationAR / VR
- 3D modeling
- Multiplayer

Languages

English Intermediate B2

Russian *Native* Ukrainian *Native*

Employment

Al Programmer - 4A Games Ukraine

Feb. 2022 – present

- Develop AI and Core systems aimed to improve interaction between player and NPCs.
- Collaborated with the design team to ensure game design and feature requirements were met.
- Researched and developed tools to improve development efficiency within the project.
- Customizing existing engine solutions and extending them to meet project needs.
- Ensuring that the features work on different platforms.

Unreal Developer 5 – Encore

Apr. 2022 - Dec. 2022

- Metaverse runner game based on combining NFT and Action multiplayer game.
- Refactor of existing code base. Improving animation management system.
- Refactor of game UI.
- Testing and optimizing app build.
- Creating an Al bot, that behaves like a player.

Unreal Developer 4 / Unity - Monolith Mind

Feb. 2021 - March. 2022

- Developing of CCG type game.
- Implementing and management of game logic, mostly related to UI.
- Debugging and fixing bugs. Improving overall experience of the game.

Unreal Developer 4 – Rogue Arts

Dec. 2018 - Sept. 2020

- Action multiplayer battle royal game.
- Develop, implement & improve new gameplay features.
- Ensure that everything is working correctly in multiplayer.
- Writing clean C++ code.

Education

The National Technical University of Ukraine "Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute"

Radio Technician - Master

2021 - 2023

Radio Technician - Bachelor

2018 – 2021